Chandan GR

Full Stack Developer

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/chandan-gr-5b18bb136/

Phone number:

9945622234

Email:

chandan2809gr@gmail.com

Address:

Bangalore, Karnataka

Nationality:

INDIAN

Education

Jain College

PUC - 91% / 100

BNMIT

BE - 71% / 100

Professional Skills

Coding Languages:

React.js, Node.js, MongoDb. Express, HTML, CSS/SCSS/JSS, Docker, Sockets, RabbitMq,

AWS, asp.net, java

Personal Profile

Highly skilled software development professional bringing more than 2.8 years in software design, development, integration and monitoring. Offering good knowledge on MERN programming language, also skilled at technical leadership communication and presentations. Experienced in handling a team and in full project life cycle from design to implementation to integratoin.

Experience

Software Developer

Manhattan Associates 07/2018 - 09/2019

- Developed and implemented software solutions based on client requirements
- Tested and refined software prior to rollout
- Designed and implemented real time Dashboards using React.js
- Implemented authentication using JWT with Node.js and Mongo.
- Created, delivered and maintained scalable code and worked on many HTML templates

Software Developer

EqTribe 09/2019 - 05/2020

- Designed, implemented form pages, Dashboards and charts using MERN.
- Developed web applications using latest React.js features like Hooks,
 Context api, antD, PWA
- Implements Responsive web pages.
- Proficient in working as application developer involving software development, debugging and performance benchmarking.

Full stack Developer

SwitchOn

05/2020 - Ongoing

- Implemented real time dashboards and charts using MERN.
- Worked on RBAC, d3.js, react-charts.js, Material UI. Have good knowledge on Docker, AWS.
- Worked on message queues like RabbitMq and chain streams and sockets on real time applications.
- Delivered performance driven and user-centric websites that met all business resqurement, reviewed code, debugging problems.

Languages

- English proficient
- Kannada proficient
- Telugu proficient
- Hindi beginner

Achievements

- Issues Journal paper on machine learning.
- Dedicated towards the work
- Self-motivated, initiative, good level of energy
- Good communication skills
- Winner of innovative project lab for 2 times conducted in college